(Sheldon:)where even the physicists
are basically engineers."
(gasps)
"Engineers"!
(Sheldon:)Do you know
how insulting that is?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Raj:)Guys, this person's
just going out of their way
(Raj:)to get a rise out of you.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but it's
still so aggravating.
Yeah, well,
(Raj:)all the other comments
said really nice things.
(Raj:)Focus on those.
Yeah.
(Howard:)Dr. Dmitri Plancovik
(Howard:)of Moscow
University said,
(Russian accent):
"Dis paper great.
(Howard:)I love it more
than 'wodka.'"
(Raj:)See? Better
with the accent.
SHELDON:
And...
(Sheldon:)send.
(Leonard:)What did you write?
(Sheldon:)I'm done hiding from bullies.
(Sheldon:)I'm taking this
into the real world.
(Leonard:)What does that mean?
I told him we'll meet him
(Sheldon:)face-to-face anytime, anywhere.
(Leonard:)Are you crazy?
You don't know who
this person is.
Delete that!
Come on, Sheldon!
(Sheldon:)Oh, okay,
(Sheldon:)okay, calm down.
(electronic tones play)
(gasps)
It's him!